question_prompts = {
    1: {
    "prompt": "Which team was on the receiving end of the largest ever defeat in Premier League history?",
    "options": ["Nottingham Forest", "Wimbledon FC", "Oldham Athletic", "Ipswich Town"],
    "answer": "Ipswich Town",
    "reveal": "Ipswich Town set the record for the heaviest ever defeat in 1995, losing 9-0 to Manchester United."
    },
    2: {
    "prompt": "Which manager holds the record for the shortest spell in charge of a club?",
    "options": ["Frank de Boer", "Paolo di Canio", "Steve Wigley", "Les Reed"], 
    "answer": "Les Reed",
    "reveal": "Les Reed's ill-fated spell as manager of Charlton Athletic ended after just 41 days in 2006."
    },
    3: {
    "prompt": "Who holds the record for the most own goals scored in the Premier League?",
    "options": ["Frank Sinclair", "Jamie Carragher", "Richard Dunne", "Wes Brown"],
    "answer": "Richard Dunne",
    "reveal": "With 10 own goals, Richard Dunne is the only player in Premier League history to hit double figures."
    },
    4: {
    "prompt": "Which team has recorded the lowest ever single season Premier League points tally?",
    "options": ["Sunderland", "Derby County", "Swindon Town", "Charlton Athletic"],
    "answer": "Derby County",
    "reveal": "Derby County managed a miserable 11 points during their 2007/08 campaign."
    },
    5: {
    "prompt": "Which player has received the most bookings in Premier League history?",
    "options": ["Kevin Davies", "Paul Scholes", "Gareth Barry", "Neil Ruddock"],
    "answer": "Gareth Barry",
    "reveal": "Barry's haul of 123 Premier League yellow cards perhaps isn't too surprising, when you consider he's the all-time appearance record holder with 653 appearances."
    },
    6: {
    "prompt": "Derby County, Ipswich Town and one other club have managed to lose a record 29 games in a single Premier League season. Can you name them?",
    "options": ["Bolton Wanderers", "Sunderland", "Coventry City", "Wolverhampton Wanderers"],
    "answer": "Sunderland",
    "reveal": "Sunderland lost 29 games en route to suffering relegation with a total points tally of 15 in 2005/06."
    },
    7: {
    "prompt": "Which player has been substituted the most times in Premier League history?",
    "options": ["Ryan Giggs", "Andy Cole", "Gary Speed", "Emile Heskey"],
    "answer": "Ryan Giggs",
    "reveal": "Having been hooked during 134 of his 632 Premier League appearances, Ryan Giggs takes this record."
    },
    8: {
    "prompt": "Which team has conceded the most goals in the history of the Premier League?",
    "options": ["Tottenham Hotspur", "Everton", "Aston Villa", "West Ham United"],
    "answer": "Tottenham Hotspur",
    "reveal": "Spurs have conceded 1,292 goals to date, having hovered around mid-table mediocrity throughout the majority of their long Premier League tenure."
    },
    9: {
    "prompt": "In 2016/17, who became the third team in the history of the Premier League to be relegated, having been top of the league earlier in the season?",
    "options": ["Middlesbrough", "Sunderland", "Hull City", "Norwich City"],
    "answer": "Hull City",
    "reveal": "Hull City were very briefly top of the pile at the beginning of the 2016/17 season, before things turned sour."
    },
    10: {
    "prompt": "Who is the only player in the history of the Premier League to register a goal, an assist, an own goal and a yellow card in a single match?",
    "options": ["Steve McManaman", "Gareth Bale", "Kevin Davies", "David Unsworth"],
    "answer": "Gareth Bale",
    "reveal": "Bale achieved this unique feat during a 2-1 win over Liverpool in 2012."
    },
    11: {
    "prompt": "Patrick Vieira, Richard Dunne and one other player have managed to get themselves sent off a record eight times. Can you name them?",
    "options": ["David Batty", "Roy Keane", "Duncan Ferguson", "Lee Cattermole"],
    "answer": "Duncan Ferguson",
    "reveal": "In addition to eight Premier League red cards, Big Dunc earned himself a three month prison sentence for headbutting an opposition player in a Scottish League match for Rangers in 1994."
    },
    12: {
    "prompt": "The lowest average attendance for a club in a single Premier League season was 10,460. Who couldn't get enough fans to their games?",
    "options": ["Swansea City", "Wimbledon FC", "Swindon Town", "AFC Bournemouth"],
    "answer": "AFC Bournemouth",
    "reveal": "Playing their home games at the maximum 11,360 capacity Vitality Stadium, AFC Bournemouth were always likely to claim this unwanted record."
    },
    13: {
    "prompt": "Who has missed the most penalties in Premier League history?",
    "options": ["Alan Shearer", "Jermain Defoe", "Steven Gerrard", "Kevin Phillips"],
    "answer": "Alan Shearer",
    "reveal": "Shearer holds the record for both penalties missed (11) and penalties scored (56) in Premier League."
    },
    14: {
    "prompt": "In the 2014/15 season, who became the fourth player to play for two relegated teams in the same Premier League season?",
    "options": ["George Boyd", "Joey Barton", "Junior Hoilett", "Robert Snodgrass"],
    "answer": "George Boyd",
    "reveal": "Boyd arrived at Burnley from Hull City midway through the 2013/14 season where both sides went down."
    },
    15: {
    "prompt": "The most goals scored by a relegated club is 55. Who holds this unwanted honour?",
    "options": ["Aston Villa", "Newcastle United", "West Ham United", "Blackpool"],
    "answer": "Blackpool",
    "reveal": "Despite scoring 55 goals, Blackpool were cosigned to relegation in 2010/11, having leaked 78 goals up the other end."
    },
}